janatabank-bd.com 2006-06-19

# Janata Privacy Policy

## 

We at Janata are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number). That is why Janata has established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information.

In general, you can visit Janata without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. 

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers which a Web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you. 

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles: 

**INFORMATION**

We want to give you information about our privacy policy and assure you that we take reasonable steps to see that it is followed within our company. 

**CHOICE**

There are times when we may collect personal information from you. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. You will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the Janata Bank Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services. 

**ACCURACY**

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us; we are working on tools that will allow you to review and update your information in the future. 

**SECURITY**

We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

**COMMITMENT**

We are committed to privacy and through our membership in and actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Personal data privacy is a new and evolving area, and Janata Bank is evolving to meet these demands. Mistakes are possible; miscommunication is possible. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [jbcomp@janatabank-bd.com](mailto:jbcomp@citechco.net) We will address any issue to the best of our abilities. 

Thank you for your support of these policies and of Janata Bank. 

|Top|         |Home|
